# **Daniel Shalem**

## Full-Stack / Frontend Developer



#### Summary

Full-Stack / Frontend Web Developer with knowledge and experience writing single-page-applications Using the latest WEB technologies such as Node.js, Vue.js, MongoDB, SASS, React.js, Svelte and React native.

M.A with Honor in international relations from Haifa University.

A team player, hard worker, focusing on problem solving and detailed orientation, self-learner responsible, and adapt quickly to new environments.

Checkout my latest Project: A single page web application that allows you to search products and quickly discover whether it's suitable for Vegans or not. Build with React.js, Node.js & MongoDB.

#### **Tech Skills**

- MVC Frameworks, Single Page Applications and PWA using Vue.js, React and Svelte.
- Server-side programming, APIs and REST with Node.js & Express.js.
- Modern JavaScript (ES6) including Object Oriented Programing.
- HTML5, CSS3 and SASS.
- React native.
- MySQL and MongoDB.

### **Professional Experience**

2020-2021: Director - Dor-labait.

Managed about 90 employees and provided service to hundreds of elderly residents of the city of Afula.

2016-2018: **Sponsorship Team Leader** – Little light Uganda.

- Developing relationships with new sponsors and managing existing relationships.
- Support above 300 children's education that lives in Namuwongo slum, one of the largest and poorest slums in Kampala, Uganda.

#### Education

2022-2022: Full stack Bootcamp - "Coding Academy".

• An intensive coding bootcamp (640 hours).

2020-2022: M.A Internaional Relations – University of Haifa.

- Specialization in negotiation and decision-making
- Finished with excellence

2016-2019: B.S.W Social work - The Max Stern Yezreel Valley College.